Guide to the David J. Skorton Presidential Liaison records, 2006-2014.
Skorton, David J. papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
David J. Skorton Presidential Liaison records, 2006-2014.
3-15-3682
David J. Skorton
6.4 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection includes files from David Skorton.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
David J. Skorton was inaugurated as president of Cornell University on September 7th, 2006.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records chronicle meetings between President David Skorton and alumni and friends of the University, foundation representatives and corporate representatives..
SUBJECTS
Names:
Skorton, David J.; Cornell University--Presidents.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University--Public relations.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.
Subjects:
College presidents--Cornell University--New York (State)--Ithaca.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin.
The Cornell University Archives Web Archive has a collection copies of speeches and essays given by President Skorton here: https://wayback.archive-it.org/2566/20140615194654/http:/cornell-classic.univcomm.cornell.edu/president/speeches/#
SERIES LIST
Series I. Meetings and Briefings
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Meetings and Briefings
  - Jeff Parker Meeting (CAM), June 2006 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1956 Reunion Panel Discussion (CAM), June 2006 (Box 1)
  - Andrew Tisch Meeting, June 2006 (Box 1)
  - Chuck Feeney Meeting, June 2006 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1971 Reunion Lunch, June 2006 (Box 1)
  - Family Fund in the Sun (1986, 1991, 1996), June 2006 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1981 Reception, June 2006 (Box 1)
  - President Skorton Phone Briefings (various), July 2006 (Box 1)
  - Howard Milstein Meeting, July 2006 (Box 4)
  - Breakfast Meeting with Sanford Weill, July 2006 (Box 1)
  - John and Janet Swanson Dinner, July 2006 (Box 4)
  - Narayana Murthy Telephone Call, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - Irwin Jacobs Telephone Call, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - Dinner with Jim and Terry Byrnes, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - James Tisch Meeting, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - Fleming Private Meeting and Dinner, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - Jeff Parker Breakfast Meeting, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - Todd Krasnow Meeting, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - Mike Zak Lunch, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - Philip R. Reilly Meeting, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - Legacy Breakfast, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - 511 CHR Neighbor Reception, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - 511 CHR Workers Lunch, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - Tompkins County Legislature, August 2006 (Box 4)
  - Tony Cashen Meeting, August 2006 (Box 1)
  - Percy Browning Reception, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - David J. Skorton Inauguration, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - 2006 Skorton Inauguration, September 2006 (Box 4)
  - Becky Morgan Meeting, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Reunion Kickoff Reception, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Presidential Councillors Dinner with President Emerti, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Presidential Councillors Meeting and Photo, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Presidential Councillors Welcome, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Presidential Councillors Reception and Dinner, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Ann Bowers Lunch, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Peter Robins Meeting (CAM), September 2006 (Box 1)
  - CAS Advisory Council, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Campaign Staff Briefing with AAandamp;D, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Atkinson Forum Dinner, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Bob and Helen Appel Lunch, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Kevin McGovern Meeting, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Ira Drukier Meeting, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Bob Katz Meeting in New York City, September 2006 (Box 4)
  - Bob Katz and Marc Kasowitz Lunch Meeting, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Robert Tishman Meeting, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Richard and Ronay Menschel Breakfast, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Don and Muffy Miller Dinner, September 2006 (Box 1)
  - Keck Foundation Visit (CAM), October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Peter Robbins Meeting, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Allan Tessler Meeting in New York City, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Paul, Irma and Howard Milstein Meeting, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Jules Kroll Meeting, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Johnson School Advisory Council Meeting (CAM), October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Major Gifts Committee Meeting in New York City, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - David Croll Breakfast, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Robert Langer Meeting, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Boston All Alumni Event – CU vs Harvard, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Bill Kay Building Dedication, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Dick Loynd Meeting, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - FHTR Exemplary Alumni Service Awards, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Cornell Alumni Federation Board Meeting, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Schoellkopf Memorial Hall Dedication, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Jessica Bibliowicz Lunch Meeting, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Sheila Johnson Breakfast, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Haider Meeting, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Jill Lerner – Informal “Meet and Greet”, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Ray Handlan Meeting (CAM), October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Ashley Luncheon in Rochester, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Zalaznick Luncheon, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Ratan Tata Meeting, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Trustee Council Scholarship Reception, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Trustee Council Dinner, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Joint Annual Meeting/Town Hall Meeting, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - TCAM Keynote Speech, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Trustee Council Reception and Dinner, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Trustee Council Cornell Fund Breakfast, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Narayana Murthy Meeting, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - AAandamp;D Staff Campaign Launch, October 2006 (Box 1)
  - Lafer Parent Reception in New York City (CAM), November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Weiss-Lynch Event, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Hatfield Reception and Dinner, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Hatfield Lecture, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Irwin and Joan Jacobs Meeting, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Konvitz Lecture, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Konvitz Reception and Dinner, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - New York City All Alumni Event – CU vs. Columbia, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Don and Jin Sook Chang Breakfast, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Jennie Chiu and Christopher Schaepe Dinner, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Daljit and Elaine Sarkaria Meeting, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - David Duffield Meeting, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - CSV Advisors Luncheon, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Tech Museum Awards Dinner, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Reeve Celebration (CAM), November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Milman Professorship Dedication (CAM), November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Milstein Dinner in New York City, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Stephan and Evalyn Milman Lunch with David Skorton, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Dick Schwartz Meeting, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Roy Park Lunch, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - David Fischell Meeting, November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Susan Lynch Professorship Dedication (CAM), November 2006 (Box 1)
  - Knight Kiplinger Meeting, December 2006 (Box 1)
  - John Dyson Meeting, December 2006 (Box 1)
  - Merryl Tisch Lunch, December 2006 (Box 1)
  - Andrew Tisch Power Breakfast, December 2006 (Box 1)
  - Cornell Entrepreneur Network (CEN) Event in New York City, December 2006 (Box 1)
  - Merrill Family Lunch in DC, December 2006 (Box 1)
  - Khoon Ean and Cheng Sui Kuok Meeting, December 2006 (Box 1)
  - Delhi All Alumni Event, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Lalit Narula Luncheon, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Cornell Club Leadership Meeting, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Mumbai All Alumni Event, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Ratan Tata Luncheon, January 2007 (Box 4)
  - Mumbai Alumni Meeting, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Pawan Goenka Meeting, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Nandlal Tolani Lunch, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Narayana Murthy Luncheon, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Bangalore All Alumni Event, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Rita Sharma Breakfast Meeting, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - James Tisch Lunch, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Barbara and Steve Friedman Dinner, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Richard Baker Meeting, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - David Opatrny Meeting, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Harold Tanner Breakfast, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Davis and Patricia Atkinson Dinner, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - CACO Luncheon in Philadelphia, January 2007 (Box 4)
  - William Kay Meeting, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Peter Robbins Lunch, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - David and Barbara Zalaznick Dinner, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Karen Burke Breakfast, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Martin Tang Meeting, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Major Gifts Committee Meeting, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - President’s Circle Dinner, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - New Life Sciences Advisory Board Meeting, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Peter Joseph Meeting, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Howard Milstein Lunch, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Jules Kroll Meeting, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Chairman’s Dinner in New Yokr City, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Richard and Ronay Menschel Dinner, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - M.H. Abrams Lecture, January 2007 (Box 1)
  - Senior Class Kickoff, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - Rhodes to attend Stewardship Visit with Sanford Reis, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - Jay Carter’s Campus Visit to Plan TCAM 2007, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - Dinner and Westminster Dog Show with Maria Niarchos-Gouaze, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - Morgens and Macaulay Dinner, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - Meeting David Skorton and L. John Wilkerson, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - Rob Dyson Meeting, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - David J. Skorton Hockey Game, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - David J. Skorton and Charlie D. Phlegar to attend Dinner meeting with Swanson’s, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - Harris Rosen Meeting, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - Alan and Elizabeth Harris Dinner, February 2007 (Box 4)
  - David Skorton to attend Pillsbury Reception and Dinner, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - David J. Skorton and Charlie D. Phlegar to attend Lunch meeting with Charles and Carol Mund, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - David Skorton to attend Lunch Meeting with Judy Biggs, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - David J. Skorton to attend Dinner with Robert and Virginia Bauer, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - David J. Skorton and Charlie D, Phlegar to meet with Ros Clark, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - David J. Skorton and Charlie D. Phlegar to meet with Barbara Kaplan prior to Reception and Dinner, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - David J. Skorton and Charlie D. Phlegar to meet with Jim and Sharie Broadhead, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - Dinner with Bob and Helen Appel, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - Meeting with Bill Nye the Science Guy, February 2007 (Box 1)
  - Meeting with Allan Tessler, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - Law School Advisory Council and Prospective Donor Dinner, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - Noyes Community Recreation Center, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - Meeting with President's Council for Cornell Women (PCCW) Chair, Margie Turner, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - PCCW Dinner, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Roy Park, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - Reception for President Skorton, West Coast LA, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - David J. Skorton to attend breakfast meeting with m/m Chang and Chris Lee, our Senior Vice President, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - David J. Skorton and Charlie D. Phlegar to meet with Peter J. Nolan, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - David J. Skorton and Jan Conrad to meet with Mr. and Mrs. Sarkarias, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - David J. Skorton and Charlie D. Phlegar to attend lunch with Doug Leone, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - David J.Skorton to attend meeting with Mike Goguen, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - Meeting with Eric Schmidt, CEO, Google, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - West Coast Tower Club, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - Cornell Silicon Valley, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - HE Advisory Council, March 2007 (Box 1)
  - Meeting with Harlan Korenvaes, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton to have lunch with Bob Abrams, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Jeff Parker, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton to meet with Dr. Sujata Naik, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton to meet with Dough and Patti Leone, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton to meet with Howard Milstein, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Robert Appel, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton/LLT to meet with Andrew Paul, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton to meet with Rob Dyson, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Andrew Tisch, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton to meet with Seth Klarman, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton to meet with Stephen Weiss, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Andrew Liveris, Dow Chemical Visit (CAM), April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Perkins Prize, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - EPE Lecture – Kevin McGovern, Speaker, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - EPE Reception and Dinner, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Johnson Graduate School of Management (JGSM) Hall of Honor Ceremony/Reception, April 2007 (Box 5)
  - JGSM Hall of Honor Dinner, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton to attend a meeting w/Jon Lindseth, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Robin L. Davisson to meet with Barbara and Les Kaplan, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Barbara Kaplan Lecture, David J. Skorton to Introduce, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Ronni Lacroute, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton meeting with Peter Robbins, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Parents Campus Visit – Welcome, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton to address the CALS Advisory Council, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Parents Campus Visit Reception and Dinner, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Rededication of Hoy Field, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton to Attend Atkinson Forum, April 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch meeting with Charles Feeney, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - New York City Tower Club, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Dinner with Richard andamp; Ronay Menschel, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Peter Joseph, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton and Charlie D. Phlegar Meeting w/David and Barbara Zalaznick, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton, Charlie Phlegar Lunch meeting with Harold Tanner, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Johnson Museum of Art Reception, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton w/Ira and Gale Drukier to present Foremost Benefactor award, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - David Skortonm Charlie Phlegar to meet with John Mellowes, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Biddy Martin to meet with David Picket (CAM), May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Biddy Martin lunch meeting with Tom Jones (CAM), May 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton to meet with Jessica Bibliowicz, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - David J. Skorton Breakfast with Abby and David Cohen, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lehman Brothers Reception and Dinner, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Barbara and Stephen Friedman, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch meeting with Edward H. Meyer, May 2007 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Leland C. Pillsbury, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Phone meeting with Chuck Feeney, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Merrill Presidential Scholars Convocation, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Merrill Scholars Luncheon, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with David and Barbara Zalaznick, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Naming Celebration for Paul Milstein Hall, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Trustee Reception/Dinner, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Sherri Steuwer, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - 2007 Senior Class Campaign Reception, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Newly Tenured Faculty Reception/Dinner, May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Dinner hosted by Jessica Bibliowicz and Nathan Bibliowicz, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Classes of 1932, 1937, 1942, 1947 Reception, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1962 Dinner, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Olin Giving Society Reception, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1957 Dinner, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1952 Reception, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Olin Lecture Luncheon, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Breakfast meeting with Chuck Feeney, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Imogene Johnson, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - State of the University Address, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1977 Lunch, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1972 Reception, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1982 Dinner, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Charles Knight, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Cornelliana Night, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Tanner Prize Luncheon, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Samuel O. Their, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch meeting with Michael Zak, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Albert J. Kaneb, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Dr. Dombrose (CAM), June 2007 (Box 2)
  - All Alumni Reception, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Telephone call to Narayana Murthy, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Breakfast meeting with Christian Bergmann, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch meeting with Andrew Kellner, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch meeting with Richard Ely, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Lubna Olayan, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Dinner with Lubna Olayan and John Xefos, June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Legacy Breakfast, August 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with David Atkinson, August 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch with Pete Meinig, David and Barbara Zalaznick, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - PCAM: Reception andamp; Dinner with Pres. Emer., September 2007 (Box 2)
  - PCAM: Private Meeting with President Skorton, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - PCAM: Reception and Dinner hosted by President Skorton, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - PCAM: Welcome to Pres. Councillors, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Ray Handlan and Steve Kresovich (CAM), September 2007 (Box 2)
  - AAandamp;D Campaign Briefing, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch with Harold Tanner, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Peter Robbins, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Bob Appel, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Telephone call to Kevin McGovern, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Andrew Tisch, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Sandy Weill, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Don and Muffy Miller Dinner, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Chuck Feeney, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Event: Hotel School 85th Anniversary, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Book Launch reception hosted by Harvey Dale, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Howard Milstein, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Dinner with Seth Klarman, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Dinner with Irwin and Joan Jacobs, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with William D. Perez (CAM) - Cancelled, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting wth Naren Shankar and Carol Mendolsohn, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Dinner with Fred Kavli, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Gary and Jerri-Ann Jacobs, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Jon Dolgen, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Luncheon with Jon Dolgen, September 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Thomas Russo, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Mr. and Mrs. Stan Taylor, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Power Breakfast hosted by Andrew Tisch (CAM), October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Gara LaMarche, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Bob Abrams, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Barbara Kaplan, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - ILR Advisory Council Meeting, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - FHTR Awards Dinner, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - CACO Board of Directors andamp; CAF Joint Meeting, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lynch/Weiss Campus Visit, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meinig Family Cornell National Scholars BBQ, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - TCAM Reception and Dinner – Thursday night, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Trustee-Council Keynote Panel, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Lalit Nirula, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Luncheon honoring Salman Rushdie, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - TCAM Reception and Dinner, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Trustee-Council Joint Annual Meeting, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Cornell Annual Fund Kick-off Breakfast, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Atkinson Forum Dinner, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Dinner hosted by Lubna Olayan and John Xefos, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Breakfast with Warren Alderige, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Tetsuo Kuboyama, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Chiaki Tanuma, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch with Alumni at Morgan Stanley, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - All Alumni Event – Tokyo, JAPAN, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - All Alumni Event – Seoul, KOREA, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Press Opportunity with Kyung-Bae Suh, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Breakfast with Stanley Lee, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Gordon Paik, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Hyun Kim Luncheon, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Tea meeting with Alex Ho, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Luncheon hosted by Martin Tang, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - All Alumni Event – HONG KONG, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Breakfast meeting with LT, Daniel, and Jeffrey Lam, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Breakfast meeting with Jonathan Zhu and Ruby Ye, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Ean Kuok, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch meeting with Kuok Family, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - All Alumni Event-Shanghai, CHINA, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - All Alumni Event-Beijing, CHINA, October 2007 (Box 2)
  - Telephone call to Howard Milstein (EPE of the Year), November 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Andy Paul and Dr. Lloyd Old, November 2007 (Box 2)
  - Phone call with Fisk Johnson, November 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Peter Joseph, November 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Keith Sinclair, November 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with David Fischell, November 2007 (Box 2)
  - Big Red Hockey Alumni Reception and Game, November 2007 (Box 2)
  - Dinner with Mr. and Mrs. Ken Derr, November 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with David Duffield, November 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch with Alex and Masud Mehran, November 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Roger Strauch, November 2007 (Box 2)
  - Park Leadership Fellows Program, December 2007 (Box 2)
  - Phone call to Harvey Dale, December 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch with Andrew and Ann Tisch, December 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch with Howard Milstein, December 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Robert Rowling Sr., December 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Richard Baker, December 2007 (Box 2)
  - Morgens/Macaulay Dinner, December 2007 (Box 2)
  - Tour and Lunch with Jay and Eileen Walker, December 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lunch meeting with Allan Tessler, December 2007 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Dr. Frederick Dombrose, January 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Martin Tang, January 2008 (Box 2)
  - Major Gifts Committee Meeting, January 2008 (Box 2)
  - New York City Campaign Reception, January 2008 (Box 2)
  - New York City Campaign Keynote, January 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Ratan Tata, January 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Leslie Nydick, January 2008 (Box 2)
  - Phone call to Patricia Carry Stewart, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Andy Paul, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Rob Dyson, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Seth Klarman, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Power Breakfast hosted by Andrew Tisch, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Fisk and Imogene Johnson, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Telephone call to Bob Appel, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Lunch with Jane M. Huttlery, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Dinner andamp; Westminster Kennel Club Dog Show, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Al and Elizabeth Harris Dinner, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with L. Sanford Reis, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Al Harris, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with M/M Robert Bauer, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Douglas Rogers, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Dinner with Barbara and Leslie Kaplan, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Charles Knight, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Coffee with James and Ruth Clark, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Lunch with Judy Biggs, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Jeff Parker, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Peter Robbins, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - 2008 Mid-winter Investment Committee Meeting and Luncheon, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Dinner with Bob and Helen Appel, February 2008 (Box 2)
  - Reception and Dinner, PCCW Annual Meeting 2008, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Andy Paul, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Karen Burke, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Jay R. Bloom, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with James Tisch, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Telephone call to Sandy Weill, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Lunch meeting with Donald Opatrny, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Allan Tessler, March 2008 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Ronay Menschel, March 2008 (Box 3)